In the not-too-distant future
Next Sunday A.D.
There was a guy named Joel
Not too different from you or me
He worked at Gizmonic Institute
Just another face
in a red jumpsuit
He did a good job
cleaning up the place
But his bosses didn't like him
So they shot him into space
We'll send him cheesy movies
The worst we can find
La-la-la
He'll have to sit
and watch them all
And we'll monitor his mind
La-la-la
Now, keep in mind
Joel can't control
Where the movies begin or end
La-la-la
Because he used
those special parts
To make his robot friends
Robot Roll Call
-Cambot
-Pan left!
-Gypsy
-Hi, girl!
-Tom Servo
-What a cool guy!
-Crow
-He's a wisecracker.
If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
And other science facts
La-la-la
Then repeat to yourself
"It's just a show, I should
really just relax"
For Mystery Science Theater 3000
Okay, Gypsy,
if you had your druthers,
what would your name be?
-Stockard Channing.
-Oh.
-What?
-Whoops.
-Oh.
Looks like we're back on,
everybody.
-Hey. Wow.
-Check it out.
Hi, everybody.
Welcome
to The Satellite of Love.
We're just talkin' about
if we had our chance,
what would our favorite
new name be? Uh, Crow?
-My name is José Jiménez.
-[ Laughs ]
-Tom Servo, what do you want?
-Well, uh--
Fifteen seconds
to commercial sign.
I've always liked the name
"Magic Voice."
Oh, I could see that.
-Oh, I--
-Huh?
Anyway, Tom Servo?
Oh, personally, I've always
been partial to Sugar Magnolia.
-Oh, yeah, Sugar Magnolia.
-[ Laughs ]
Commercial sign in five,
four, three, two--
Commercial sign now.
And from now on,
I'll be known as Chuck Woolery.
We'll be back in two minutes
and two seconds.
Open.
-Joel? Joel?
-Yeah, Crow, buddy?
Would it be okay if I changed
my name to Alan Parsons Project?
They call me Mr. Tibbs.
[ Laughs ]
Mrs. Richard Dysart,
Mrs. Richard Dysart.
From now on, I'll be known
as Vivienne Mayes.
That's it, that's it.
From now on, all bets are off.
From now on, we go back
to the old names
for the rest of the experiments.
The Mads are calling.
You know, Clay, when
you come right down to it,
I think I'd like to be known
as just...
-Frank.
-Why is that, Frank?
Because if you can't find peace
within--
Oh, shut up.
I don't think
there's any hope in--
I went along with you
long enough.
This furniture there
was a terrible idea.
Don't I get to be
your co-host for the week?
No, and you don't get to sing
"The Man in my Little
Girl's Life" either.
Oh, hello, booby,
how did you fare going
through the asteroid belt?
Jeepers, don't remind me.
Ouch!
Well, my invention exchange
this week is-
Wait for it.
Daddy, there's a boy outside.
-His name is-
-Shut up. Now.
Everybody knows
smoking kills, but it's cool.
-Hmm.
-What are you gonna do?
Everybody loves tar.
Sure, who doesn't?
But scientists have known
for well over a year
that it's bad for you.
So, when you go
into a restaurant,
and they ask you for Smoking
or Non-Smoking, do what I do.
Hey, it's a smoking jacket.
-Ah, cool.
-Get it?
Like father, like son.
Think about it, won't you?
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, right.
Well, here it is, dimples,
the latest craze:
robotic arm-wrestling.
[ Whistle blows ]
[ Grunts, laughs ]
[ Grunts ]
I can't-- Oh.
[ Groans ]
-Frank!
Frank! Hoo-hoo!
-Yes! [ Laughs ]
-Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Forrester, Forrester,
Dr. Clayton Forrester!
Whoo!
Frank!
-Shh!
-Whoo!
-[ Groans ]
-Yes! Yes!
[ Groans ]
[ Whistle blows ]
Whoo!
Whoo hoo hoo!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Uh, well, uh,
your experiment this week,
Joel, is a bit of a break
for you. Uh, it's, uh, it's--
I haven't seen the whole thing,
but it's kind
of a buddy picture.
I've seen the opening credits,
and it looks to be
ike a modern-day "Defiant Ones".
Isn't that right, Frank?
I think you're gonna like it.
It's a little thing
we like to call "Cave Dwellers".
Frank!
Enjoy it while it lasts,
Astroboytoy.
[ Panicked reactions ]
My gosh.
Oh, this must be in, uh,
shoebox format here.
-Yeah.
-Neat.
[ Sighs ]
How much Keeffe is
in this movie, anyway?
"Miles O'Keeffe."
-[ Chuckles ]
-Huh?
Hey, now, look,
here you can actually see
the driver turn
and shoot Kennedy.
[ Chuckles ]
It's-- I'm not gonna-- Uh.
Cavé Dwellers?
Wasn't he in, uh--?
-Cave. Cave Dwellers.
-Oh.
It's the name of the movie.
-I'm guessing.
-Hey, Jodie Foster's sister.
I'd shoot Donald Regan to prove
my love for Lisa Foster.
[ Chuckles ]
It's cute. Uh-huh. Yeah.
I see it.
Hm. Borromel: the thorough
but gentle laxative.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, isn't this a scene
from Brian's Song?
Yeah, that's, uh,
Billy Dee Williams
and James Caan.
-Oh.
-I love Brian Piccolo,
and when you hit
your knees tonight,
ask God to love him, too.
Hey, bro. Let's go get a brew.
Come on.
David Cain Haughton.
Wasn't he an assassin?
No, you're thinkin'
of Lee Harvey Oswald.
-No, it was James Earl Ray.
-Uh, no. Mark David Chapman.
-No, John Wilkes Booth.
-No, it was Arthur Bremer.
Huh?
-Arthur Bremer?
-Oh.
-Oh, well, okay, well.
Director of the top half
of the photography.
-There it is.
-Wow, a lot going on back there.
-You guys should check it out.
-Hey, look. Rustichelli.
That's good
with a little pesto sauce
and some sun-dried tomatoes.
[ Chuckles ]
-Italian thing.
-Those poor bastards.
This is ridiculous.
-Huh? Oh. Oh. Oh.
-Thought it was over there.
Wow.
Turning the page
in the middle--
Hey, John Newman.
We can put his spaghetti sauce
on the Rustichelli.
[ Laughs ] That's good.
Yeah.
Ooh...
Poor guy.
The Hills Have Eyes.
But they have glaucoma
right now. [ Chuckles ]
[ Hum ]
That was close, friend.
This week on Cave Dwellers.
Uh, I'm grinding the basil,
add--
adding some romano cheese.
Hm.
-[ Chewing noises ]
-Mm, Grog taste good.
Hey, it's the cast party
for Cats.
It's Betty Buckley, and
she's eating Dick Van Patten.
-[ Laughs ]
-Ew.
A little stringy.
You know, you can eat
off the floor of this cave.
In fact, they're doing it
right now.
After the fiery chaotic creation
of the Earth,
in the turbulent period
of Man's ascendancy...
Hey, who's talking?
...our world was populated by
wild, cruel and ignorant men.
-Oh, you mean the '80s.
-But there are still a few
who seem to have been touched
by some higher power.
-And they're in AA now.
-Yeah.
Hey, get out of the fire.
But their table manners
needed work.
Playing the center spear:
Og!
Playing defensive backup:
Oog!
And at right hunchback,
it's Org!
-[ Hums a dramatic tune ]
-[ Whistles ]
Hey, there's a monolith outside!
Yeah, everybody's evolving
and stuff. It's really neat!
Hey, Grog just threw a bone
into the air,
and it turned into a spaceship.
Come on, come on.
-Cro-magnon.
-Neanderthal.
-Australopithecus Africanus.
-Why you--
Come on, get in the line,
get in the line.
The Time Life photographer
is here.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, it's the Gorgeous Ladies
of Wrestling.
[ Growls ]
-Ooh.
-Hey.
How can they tell whose side--?
Who's on whose side?
-Oh, it's, uh, shirts and skins?
-Oh.
-[ Groans ]
-Skins. [ Chuckles ]
Eat it, boy. Eat it.
Ouch. Ooh.
Oh, it's the man
who invented the wedgie.
-Oh.
-[ Applauds ]
-How nice.
-Yeah.
It's an early version
of West Side Story.
Uh, I just met a girl named Uh.
Stately Wayne Manor.
-Wow, it's Barbi Benton.
-Hef, we're all out of Evian.
You called me, Father?
Are you still here?
What's the matter?
Um, I'm all out of blue stuff.
I've never seen you
looking so worried.
Or so ashamed.
st night, I had a strange dream.
About a chick in a black bikini.
It troubled me greatly.
Human knowledge,
even in its most exalted form...
-Uh-huh.
-...is nothing...
-Mm-hm.
-...against fate.
-Come over here, my dear.
-To where the camera moved to.
There's something
I must show you.
Over here.
-[ Whistles ]
-Hey.
Father, dear,
you've always shared
your knowledge
and inventions with me.
Is there something
you've discovered
that you've been hiding
from me?
I've always wanted you
to be wise.
But we'll settle on looks.
But remember that imagination
is as important as knowledge.
-Hm?
-Yes, imagination.
-Ah.
-Oh.
-And this you possess by nature.
-Mm, neat.
The next most important thing...
-...is prudence.
-Is peanut butter.
But this man learns only
with the passage of time.
More than you.
I've waited until now
to show you my discovery.
A rear-view mirror?
-Stronger than dirt.
-What is it?
It is everything and nothing.
Uh, could you be
a little more vague, please?
It is life and death.
Goodness...
-And badness.
...riches and poverty. And evil.
-It's boss!
-Neat.
It all depends on Man.
-What are Man's options?
-What Man does with it.
Oh.
-Okay.
-Then, it might...
-[ Window-wiping noise ]
-...might be a weapon.
-Exactly.
-Mm-hm.
And like all weapons,
it must be kept
away from ambitious men.
-Ah.
-And Nazis.
But, Father, how can I save it?
No, daughter, your hands
are too weak.
You'll get fingerprints
all over it.
Zor's thirst for power...
...is too strong.
He's heading south
with his henchmen.
I know.
I can see myself in there.
But he would never dare
to enter our territory.
I wonder if it's worth the risk
of counting on that.
Or the risk of acting.
But, Father, you taught me
that science is always a risk.
Ah, but a man of science
takes a calculated risk.
Mm.
Science is only a means,
one of many, to obtain...
-There is also fan dancing.
-Ooh.
What do you,
the viewers at home, think?
I am now too old
for so great a responsibility.
And for such flashy jewelry.
What do you intend doing?
To protect a thing
of such great import...
tance!
There is only one man.
Ator.
-But he's a baby.
-Ator is the son of Torren.
He was born during the tenebrous
era of the Spider Kingdom.
Wow, everybody did drugs then,
I guess.
--in the service of Dakkar
and his spotted high priest,
-...were sent out to--
hese must be Ator's home movies.
--former high priest carried off
the infant Ator to safety.
Uh, this is the part of the film
we like to call
"She Had to Ask".
--the black knights--
-Yep.
ho constantly scoured the land--
-Uh-huh.
--sacrificial victims
of the Spider God.
Spider God, uh-huh.
Sweeping down upon the village
where Ator, now a young man--
Yeah.
--black knights badly wounded
him and carried off Sunya,
his young bride.
-Gettin' all this?
-Say.
Whoa.
-As Ator nursed his wounds...
-I nursed a scotch.
...he swore to rescue Sunya
and crush the iron-handed rule
of Dakkar.
Who?
Griba...
Son of Flogmug, Keeper
of the Seven Keys of Pentoozler.
...encouraged Ator
and taught him the martial arts.
And Marshall Crenshaw.
Marshall Tucker.
ings are movin' real fast. Whoo.
-Yeah.
-Enjoy it while it lasts.
-Hey, Jean Kasem.
When Ator was deemed ready
to set out on his mission,
-...Griba revealed-...
-Say. Nice.
...noble heritage and consigned
to him the Sword of Torren.
No, the shroud of Turin.
Sheesh.
Geez. Tolkien
couldn't follow this plot.
- [ Snores ]
-Not enough dwarves.
-It's the Wango the Tango!
-Whoo!
Get down.
Before Ator could conquer
the Spider Kingdom,
he came under the spell
of the beautiful witch Indun.
Ooh, Cher at the funhouse.
A thousand-year-old
enchantress...
-Yick.
-Ugh.
...who called forth a horrible
army of walking dead. Of slaves.
It's Aztec mommy!
Ooh, how graphic.
-Wow.
-Check me out, I'm not half bad.
--captured the glistening
charmed shield of Murdor.
And the secret decoder ring.
Oh, come on. Those moon boots
went out in the '70s.
At last, Ator confronted Dakkar.
Played by Tommy Chong.
...and his gruesome
deformed warriors
in a battle to the death.
Oh, he's been gonged.
Whoa.
Aided by the incredibly potent
shield of Murdor...
-And its free prize inside.
-...the malicious priest...
...then had to kill Griba, who
had revealed his evil designs
for obtaining power
by using Ator as his pawn.
Then he broke for a light lunch.
After rescuing Sunya...
Ator faced the immense,
hideous spider itself...
Ee.
...and plunged
the Sword of Torren
into the grisly creature's body.
He'd never killed, uh,
that big a puppet before.
When the Spider God was killed,
the forces of blackest evil
were unleashed--
Uh, objects in shield are
smaller than they appear.
--forth its molten magma
in anger.
Then he worked out
on the charismatic solo flex
of Zontar 13.
[ Grunts ]
Now rest. You deserve it.
[ Chuckles ]
Later, when Sunya died, Ator
retired to the eastern land,
where he lives
in the company of Thong,
an Oriental warrior and savior.
Played here by Jimmy Carl Black
of The Mothers of Invention.
[ Sharp scratching noise ]
-Ooh, I hate that.
-That's enough for now, Thong.
Uh, scratching, that is.
You know, that exercise works.
You were right.
-I can feel it here.
-Wait, where's my shirt?
The muscles are stronger.
Yeah.
-Are we still in a flashback?
-Ah--
-I think so.
-I don't know.
[ French accent ] Cato.
Whoa.
You get to be
a teppanyaki chef.
Yeah.
-Am I still usin' that old move?
- [ Chuckles ]
Ha, ha, hey, kiba!
You should see him
with vegetables.
Okay.
Oh, not done yet. Hai!
[ Slashing noises ]
Then they do improv exercises.
Whoo.
Align the vertebrae,
and release.
And break.
Shake it out.
There.
That'll do.
Now, where was I?
Charmed shield,
incredibly potent--
-Father?
- [ Startled gasp ]
Yes, my dear?
-Tell me.
-Again?
-No!
-No, no, no!
[ Sighs ]
All right.
Daughter...
you know you're
the only person...
Oh, I know what's gonna happen.
...who could recognize
the urgency of my cause.
Mm-hm.
But I can't leave you
at a time like this.
During a flashback.
Dear, you will find
with the passing of time
that you can't always have
what you want.
But if you try sometimes,
you just might find you get
what you need.
But you're the only one I have.
-You and the duck.
-My dear Mila.
You don't have to worry
about my safety.
A sly old fox like me knows
how to take care of himself.
These are things a man
has to learn.
Quit shakin' me, Dad.
And goes on repeating
for the rest of life,
unfortunately.
-What?
-Stately Wayne Manor.
What's Wayne Manor?
Oh, that's where Batman
lived before he, uh, became
The Dark Knight
in those comic books.
Oh, they're not comic books,
they're graphic novels.
-Oh.
-Come on.
Music
by The Super Mario Brothers.
[ Effort grunts ]
- [ Horse whinnies ]
- [ Effort grunts ]
[ Grunts ]
Quit pushin' back there. Ooh.
Keep your swords down,
you're inside now.
That city's supposed to be
around here somewhere.
-Let's see.
-Follow me!
-We are.
-Uh, we're trying.
-Which--? Oh, that--? Oh, okay.
-This way!
- [ Clearing throats ]
- [ Whistles ]
[ Shouting ]
Run outside and see
what the trouble is, quickly!
-But you--
-Go, I told you.
-And be careful.
-Huh?
[ Excited breath ]
Later. Later.
[ Whistles ]
Well, better 86 the hooch.
A little nip won't hurt.
[ Hums ]
[ Attack yells ]
Use the handrails.
Safety on the stairway.
-Hey, wait for me.
-Me, too.
Hey, wait up. Hey,
I found some funny wet clay.
-It's raining men, hallelujah.
-Whew.
[ Fighting noises ]
Yee-hoo!
-Dad, tell me another story.
-Zor is here.
I should have realized
the time was so close.
I've read the script.
You must ride due east
and try to reach Ator.
The road's long and hard...
[ Pneumatic
tube-sucking noises ]
When you seem to have reached
the ends of the earth--
Ask for Earl.
--and it seems
that nature herself
declines to accompany you
any further on your journey,
then you will have reached
the domain of Ator.
Canada?
How can you ask me
to do this now?
It is not for myself that I ask,
Mila,
but for the welfare
of all mankind.
Ah.
Go.
Take a sweater.
And be back by 10!
Hi.
[ Struggling noises ]
Huh?
-That's my spice rack!
-Aw.
[ Groans ]
-Dad?
-Poor guy.
Stop!
-Huh?
-Hm?
How dare you lay hands on him,
you mangy dogs?
All of you put together are not
worth this man's little finger.
And I mean that from
the bottom of my heart.
Out!
Help me.
You know, that hat has
a slimming effect on you.
I thought that among
your many virtues...
Mm-hm?
...the first I'd find
was forgiveness.
Oh, I'm sorry. I-
Perhaps I've not yet
quite acquired...
total control...
-Of--?
-...over myself.
Come, they are only
petty soldiers.
They can't approach
your exalted level.
Oh, thanks,
but now's no time to kiss up.
My life comes to an end,
all levels, I would say.
Really?
Now... for my own part,
I fail to see why during life...
Uh-huh?
...we create artificial
distinctions between ourselves.
-Mm-hm.
-Hm.
Because all men
are born equal.
Oh, let me get a pencil,
I wanna write that one down.
Makes me sick.
I've become more
and more certain
that my little visit here...
-Mm-hm?
-...was fully justified
and will be
extremely profitable.
You can write it off
on your taxes.
-Mm-hm.
-Do you imply...
-Mm-hm?
-...that you are a conqueror...
Mm-hm?
...who claims
the spoils of victory?
Or are you...
...a common...
...thief?
Oh, Geez, this has more pauses
than a Pinter play.
[ Laughs ]
- [ Laughs ]
-Oh, observational humor.
God, I love Seinfeld.
-Oh, we gotta get outta here.
-Let's go.
In this case, let's just say
I'm an unexpected guest.
-Ooh! Ooh!
- [ Laughs ]
Ah! Ah! Too tight.
-Oh, oh.
-Whoa, there.
I don't know, Joel.
I don't think this is for me.
Whoops, I lost it.
Uh, it's okay.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
You look fantastic.
I could eat ya up.
Oh, and I could bite
that big toe.
-Ooh hoo hoo.
-Hey, now, quit clowning.
You know, what we're gonna do
is a more lucid version
of those really bad, uh,
openings we saw.
-The credits, you know?
-Oh, the credits, yeah.
Hey, that is if Cambot will man
the wall of keyboards.
-What do you say?
-Oh, good.
Hey, and will you give us
that half-screen, uh,
posterization effect too,
Cambot?
-There we go.
-Uh, Joel...
--uh, what are we
supposed to do again?
That's cool.
Well, all you do is we play
the characters
we talked about earlier
and we run around and stuff.
All right, got it.
Frolic, cavort, parade,
gad about the ship,
that sorta thing.
-Uh, Joel?
-Yeah?
Isn't this kinda fruity?
Gee, I never really thought
about it that much.
-Joel, it is.
-Yep.
Well, no matter.
Anyway, uh, let's do it again.
-You ready, Cambot?
-Music. Here we go.
[ Swords noise ]
[ Fighting grunts ]
I thought that was pretty fun.
-Yeah.
-It was cool. [ Laughs ]
She's still looking
for the ends of the Earth here.
Ends of the Earth,
ends of the Earth,
I gotta get to the ends
of the Earth.
Ends of the Earth,
ends of the Earth.
[ Pants ]
- [ Screams ]
-Ooh, she's in love.
So the ends of the Earth
are this way.
Thank you.
[ Grunts ]
You idiot.
We don't even have
a doe license.
That way.
Yeah.
Ends of the Earth-- En--
Ends of the Earth-- [ Groans ]
Let me see, uh, you were
playing a Titleist, right?
Yep.
You got a rotten lie,
let me tell ya.
Daddy--
Uh, uh, lady, can we have
our arrow back?
Lady? Oh, Mrs. Lady!
Oh-- [ Snorts ]
Ah.
Hey, why is she limping?
'Cause she's got an arrow
in her chest.
Oh, I can see-- Huh?
One thing still puzzles me,
Akronas.
Use the handrails.
I invented them for a reason.
Why east?
Why did your daughter
fly like an arrow
straight towards the sun?
Ooh, good metaphor.
Of course, I could easily use
torture to make you tell me,
but that would too simple.
-And too much fun.
-Spoil our little game.
Yes.
I see.
It's quite obvious
that you're testing me.
You want to verify
my powers of deduction.
-Mm-hm.
-Very well.
-Nice.
-Bring me the map.
And bring me the head
of Gallagher.
[ Bird sounds ]
[ Horse whinny ]
[ Engine noise ]
Shh.
- [ Wind noise ]
-Welcome to Death Valley Days.
The driver's either missing
or he's dead.
[ Chuckles ]
Say...
Made this in shop class.
It's a letter opener.
It's not perfect yet.
A Mark Seven Production.
[ Hums ]
He doesn't give a tinker's damn
about anything.
Nope.
[ Owl noise ]
Hey, did you just turn into
an owl and then back real fast?
-Maybe it was too hot.
-Mm.
-Mm-hm.
-It should be enough for now.
-Gotta wait until it's cold.
-That could take forever.
Oh, help!
-Huh?
-Hm?
Run! Look out, it's wet there!
I just mopped.
Ator, help me, please.
-Prepare everything for her.
-With pleasure, my liege.
-Hey, he's washing with lava.
-The soap?
Oh, no, the real thing.
-Hm.
- [ Chuckles ]
-It's Marmaduke.
- [ Dog panting ]
[ Dog panting ]
All right, good.
Okay, let's see.
We've got the cow skin,
the banana leaves and the dog.
That should be about everything.
All we can do is pray,
although we haven't thought
of any gods yet.
Well, it's up to the dog.
No, Marmaduke!
Don't use the triple over
end stitch! Bad dog!
[ Whines ]
I could be wrong,
but this arrow might have
something to do with her pain.
Ah.
[ Licks, whines ]
-What do we got?
-She's okay.
Yeah.
Boy!
Look at how primitive
their wet naps
were during the dark ages.
Mm.
Yeah, it's a pretty big hole.
I might need
another one of those.
[ Chuckles ]
Got the crazy idea, boss.
Let's make a giant cigar
out of her.
What?
Would you quit your--?
The entire area is deserted,
barren.
It's the best show tune ever!
It's brassy, sassy,
it's a musical humdinger!
Let's see...
[ Speaks in Latin ]
Wait a minute.
-Ator!
-This is the magna carta!
So now we have it.
He was another pupil of yours,
wasn't he?
Hm, kind of impressed
about his part in this film,
isn't he?
Many stories have grown up
around this pupil of yours.
I wish you'd grow up.
But now the time has come...
-...for me to discover...
-The manchild within.
...proof of these stories.
I pledge allegiance--
This is really amazing.
Hm.
Why, your knowledge of surgery
surpasses even that
of The Great One.
Who, Jackie Gleason?
Oh, I'm just tallying up
your bill here.
I'm ready to go now.
No, you're not going.
-I'll decide when you're ready.
-Little missy.
-Journey is long.
- [ Hums ]
Once we start,
there'll be no stopping.
But I explained to you
that my father
is in great danger.
Danger--
How many A's in "danger"?
I understand the dangers
that face all men.
All...
...men.
The wise one is very strong.
-..ry strong.
-And will resist.
But his heart is weak.
-Heart is weak.
-That's the reason he sent me.
-Sent me.
-What do you think he's writing?
-The script?
-Yeah.
Huh.
All right.
But you must know this--
Two plus two is fi--
I mean, four.
If you're too weak...
we'll have to leave you behind.
Oh, thanks for the beer,
Gomez.
But first you
must prove to us...
if you are the daughter
of The Great One.
If you can look bored
and speak haltingly, you're in.
Come with me.
No, not you, her.
There she is.
Too bad Gomez
didn't get a speaking role here.
Poor guy.
Go in there.
Oh, right, I'm a freshman
at a small Midwestern college.
The small one
was dark with long hair.
Mila.
Now sing something
from Paint Your Wagon.
If you're really
the daughter of Akronas...
Kronos Quartet? Oh.
...then, you will know
what to do.
Okay.
Next on Current Affair:
"Women Behind Bars"!
[ Hums Current Affairs theme ]
Hm, okay.
Let's see now,
there's a Superball
and half a peanut
and a length of kite string
and a carpenter's saw.
What would McGyver do?
Is this right?
-Hm. Mm-mm.
-No, wrong, cold.
Very cold.
-Freezing.
-Frigid.
-Freezing. Alaska.
-Mhm.
Oh, you're a cute one,
aren't ya?
[ Chuckles ]
Getting warmer.
-Hm, warm as toast.
-She made, uh--
Very warm.
She's making flash powder
from her own filth.
-Oh, neat.
- [ Vomiting noise ]
Yee.
-Uh-huh.
-Dibs.
Rats.
Uh-oh.
Oh.
[ Singing ] Love, love, love!
Tu, tu, tu
They do have a lot of product
to burn off.
Mm-hm.
Hm. I suppose she could
have just tried the lock.
All done?
Uh, Gomez, don't pass
in front of the actors.
Please.
When I left
your father's castle,
he told me that if ever
the geometric nucleus
could endanger
the world's peace...
Huh?
...a messenger
would come to me
and prove his identity
beyond a doubt.
You owe me 50 bucks
for the door.
-Let us go.
-Ancient Chinese secret, huh?
Let's say that thanks
to your teaching,
Ator has mastered
the forces of nature.
Well, my dear Akronas,
let me introduce you to Sandur.
You can call me Sandy.
He represents,
how shall I put it?
The opposite
of your pupil, Ator.
Looks like, uh, Willie Nelson,
doesn't he?
Hm.
--has mastered
everything that lies
outside and beyond
the forces of nature.
-And he knows Liza.
-He manipulates at will
those forces which men
believe uncontrollable.
-Mm-hm.
-The occult.
-Oh.
-The IRS.
-Yes.
-What do you say to that?
Many years ago...
-Oh, not another flashback!
-No, no, no, no, no, no!
-It's cool.
-...rough with magic.
-For hire, they--
- [ Snores ]
Dear God, he's dull.
Of course, any man who seeks
knowledge and is wise...
should be willing...
See if you can make him
slow down, Joel.
Who knows?
-Hey. Hey up there.
-I myself can learn.
So as you can see...
Man, Willie Nelson's
a tough audience.
.giving us a lesson in humility.
Nevertheless...
Hey, doesn't he make
leather mugs
at the Renaissance Festival?
...and you will see
a flame of defiance.
Say something.
Line.
Come on.
Fake it.
Yes, it is clearly there.
-Mm.
-And that's my only line.
Good.
Sandur, there is
someone I want...
...neutral.
Eliminated.
What happened?
-Jump cut.
-Where is he?
Far away.
-At the ends of the Earth.
-Canada.
Could you find
a more convenient place?
And who is it, sire?
-Ator.
-Gesundheit.
t's the chalice from the palace.
And now you will witness
the might of my power.
Got a minute?
-Ooh!
-Whoa!
Oh.
-Yowza.
-Cool.
Doodelee doodelee doodelee.
-Things gettin' kinda weird.
- [ Musical noises ]
Say, I think your cape
is fabulous!
[ Chuckles ]
They're getting close
to Ridley Scott now.
I don't understand.
We're not surprised.
Are these guys
employed by anybody?
I think they're just temps
wandering through the forest.
-Yeah.
-Hire-a-Thug.
Uh-oh.
This fog's starting
to obscure the action.
-What action?
-Oh.
[ Clears throat ]
Whose woods are these?
I think I know.
Now watch these woods
fill up with fog.
And where's Mila?
Who?
Mila!
Puma!
She must be lost.
I say, it's foggy.
Guys, this isn't funny.
-Guys-
-Ator!
Mila!
Puma!
Ah!
-Don't do that.
-Where are you?
[ Clears throat ]
Did someone say "Ator"?
Paging Mr. Ator.
Hm.
- [ Coughs ]
-Yeah.
After exhausting
every possibility,
the men move on.
Who knew there was a cave
like this in these parts?
-Wilma? Barney!
-Someone's following us.
Echo!
- [ Roar ]
-Good one.
Did you hear that?
Listen.
[ Roar ]
Come on.
Quick, run with me, friend.
Towards the danger.
Boy, wonder how much
it costs to heat this cave.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Gasps ]
Ooh.
-Huh?
-They're invisible!
Huh!
- [ Laughs ]
-Oh, man.
I don't believe it.
They were too cheap
to hire a villain in this movie.
-Yep.
- [ Roaring ]
Imitates the screen's roaring ]
Oh, come on, what is this?
A Charlie Callas routine?
[ Mocks sound effects ]
Ooh.
[ Blow ]
Hey, why don't you pick
on somebody
your own opacity, huh?
[ Laughs ]
-What is this? A Heart video?
-Yeah.
They only show the fat one
from the head up anymore.
-Hey.
-Sorry, that was a little--
Dad?
-Guy.
-Play Misty for Me.
So let's recap the action
so far.
Uh, nothing really.
Ah, you're right.
Let's move on now.
- [ Roar ]
-Dad?
- [ Blow ]
- [ Laughs ]
[ Blow ]
Hey, why do you keep
hittin' yourself?
[ Goofy laugh ]
Dork.
[ Startled yell ]
Oh, now they're scarier!
Whoa!
Booga booga booga booga.
I do this to my dog.
It's really funny.
[ Growls, barks ]
No, they're not scary,
they're just kinda goofy.
[ Growls, barks ]
[ Yelps ]
Like shootin' fish
in a barrel, Dong.
-Uh, "Thong".
-Oh, that's it.
Come on, just kill it.
Don't play with it.
Good boy.
Man, don't they want
their capes?
No, they'd have
invisible blood on 'em.
Oh, I-- Wha--?
Daddy, so long as we're here,
can we stop over at The Gap
and get some 501s?
Huh?
Oh, well, like, excuse me,
have you seen, uh,
two guys with capes?
-Ew, grody Jody.
- [ Cackles ]
No, God, I don't want
a sample Giorgio.
[ Fighting grunts ]
Hey.
-Oh, no.
-Who are these guys?
Oh, these must be
the cave dwellers.
That's right,
35 minutes into the film,
and we're finally
at the first plot point.
-Ooh.
-Well, there's Sid Field.
Hey, I hate Clinique.
Really, I'm just looking.
Huh?
You go there.
I'll go this way.
-We'll stick--
-Uh, no, no.
It's walk softly
and carry a large club.
No, no, it's quickly walk
and carry something big.
No, I know it's speak softly
and carry a--
Nah, you're crazy, you walk
swiftly and you carry--
You carry something.
-I know you carry something.
-No, no, no, you're walking--
-No!
-Okay!
Oh, no!
Gah.
Thatch?
Coppola!
-Dad?
- [ Caveman chatter ]
"Ojibwa"! Wait a minute,
I invented a word!
Huh.
-Hmm.
- [ Caveman chatter ]
Uh, rhubarb.
Caveman rhubarb.
I am a noble savage.
Huh?
Look at that.
God, I hate Mondays.
Boo.
There's that great Hammond
organ sound.
Ugh, now we steal your hubcap.
[ Chuckles ]
Get lug wrench.
Tuesdays are Human Sacrifice Day
at The Sizzler.
Guy.
- [ Grunts ] Barbecue 'em.
- [ Laughs ] Oh.
Ew.
Ah.
I think Tony Bennett
left that in San Francisco.
Ew.
-Here, it's a little rare.
-Yeah.
[ Groan ]
[ Laughs ]
I won a Barney Clark heart.
[ Sniffing ]
Mm, something smells good.
[ Caveman chatter ]
Ugh, cannibal rhubarb.
Ugh.
Ator comes out of the hole,
'round the fire-
Sees his shadow.
Hey, it's Dr. Christian Barnard.
-What do you know?
-Was.
[ Angry caveman chatter ]
Hey.
He said, "Hey".
Hey, you know, now
this really is a Heart video.
[ Laughs ]
With the thing and--
Eh.
Ew. Greasy dirt.
Huh? Uh, you say something,
God?
Ooh, she got childproof cap.
I've got a wonderful
Grinchy idea.
[ Chuckles ]
Hm.
Hey, she already has a plate.
She-- She's self-serving.
Oh, speakin' of serving,
we gotta run.
-Let's go, guys.
-Oh, yeah. We gotta go.
Ooh! It's a light
and sound spectacular!
It's just getting' cool, too.
[ Frightened caveman chatter ]
-Uh-huh.
-Uh, say, Joel?
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, ask away,
my red friend.
[ Laughs ] Why is it
these guys in the film
give such fancy pants names
to everything, hm?
Yeah, like, they call
a regular old shield
"the glimmering charm shield".
-It's, like, so stupid. Guy.
-Indeed.
Well, it's obvious this movie
has a really low budget.
-Especially for props.
-Mm-hm. Yeah.
And so by adding really neat
names to ordinary things...
-...you can kind of dress it up.
-Oh.
Like, it was kind of obvious
her breastplate
that the woman was wearing
was actually an off-the-rack
auto part from NAPA.
-Oh.
-But you can't very well say,
"Hither yon, there goes
the hubcap of the
Plymouth Somerset," right?
Right! But what
you could say is,
"She has donned the maiden
shield of Bally Seven.
-Exactly, now you're getting it.
-Yeah, I-- I get it. I see.
Um, if I had a box of ordinary
paperclips, uh, I could say, um,
"Here is a box of incredibly
bent pieces of wire
used to hold the pressed wood
pulp planes in security."
Right, now you're getting it.
That's exactly right.
It's just adding extraordinary
names to ordinary things.
-It makes it fun.
-Yeah, yeah.
You find the fun and snap,
the job's a game. [ Laughs ]
-Thank you, Mary Poppins.
-Yeah, spit spot, you two.
Oh, I love to laugh,
long and loud and clear.
- [ Laughs ]
-Oh, get on, laughing.
[ Clears throat ]
Oh, sorry, I digress.
Um, well, anyway, you know,
they give cool names
to TV shows like that, too.
Like, uh, White Shadow--
--could've been called, uh,
Haloed Hoop Honky.
- [ Laughs ]
-Or, uh...
Jake and the Fatman, you
could've called that um, well--
--uh, Jake and the Fatman.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, yeah.
You know what occurs to me?
That when local TV stations
talk about the grand marshals
for their holiday parades,
what they're really saying
is Gavin MacLeod.
-Exactly.
-Oh, I got one.
A pre-recorded segment
that's, uh-
that goes into a program
is called a bumper.
-Oh, yeah?
-And actually it's really just--
- [ Buzzer sounds ]
-The movie's s--
[ Scream and yell ]
-Oh, wow.
- [ Chuckles ]
[ Clears throat ]
Oh, boy.
Well, let's see, uh, "He who
reads these words of wit
eats these little balls--"
Oh, now that's immature,
even for The Dark Ages.
Hm, "For a good time,
call Dong."
-Thong.
Here's-- Huh?
- [ Fighting noises ]
- [ Chuckles ]
They're kinda dumb,
they're easy to kill:
the American Gladiators.
Hm.
Ah.
-Hm.
-Something dull.
Come towards it, our friend.
By the stubbing of my thumb,
something stupid this way comes.
Aha, just as I thought.
-Hm.
-Checks out.
Meter man.
Knock it off up there.
Huh? "For a good time, call--"
Oh.
Stupid rock.
Stupid, stupid rock.
Get-- Oh. Oh, man.
Did you find a way out?
Stupid rock.
Good thing you were here,
Gomez.
We woulda never found it
without you.
Huh?
"Drizzle drazzle drozzle drone,
time for zis one to come home."
So Bob Hope owns all of that?
Yeah, yeah. We're thinkin'
of turning it into a 9-holer.
-Hm.
-Yeah.
-You have failed, Sandur.
-Bad country singer.
-Bad Willie.
-You made me lose precious time!
If you had all the magical
powers you told me you had--
Again with the finger.
I don't see how I failed.
You don't, eh?
Well, you soon will.
Guards!
Hey, Paul Wellstone.
You'd think after all this time,
Sandur has been worthy
of your esteem.
And you are as guilty
of having failed as he is.
-Flog him!
-Thank you, sir.
-Please have mercy.
-I fear for you, Sandur.
Mercy does not dwell
in the hearts of those
without spiritual strength
and wisdom.
Oh, bite me. It's fun.
Very well.
Imprison him.
I'll employ some tricks
of my own against Ator
and you can use your time
to come up with something new
and it better be good, Sandur,
if you want to regain my esteem.
And I think you know how
important for you is my esteem.
Hm.
Okay. Okay,
I'll do linking rings.
I'll do bottom of the cup.
I'll do metamorphosis.
Wait! Wait!
It's here.
Oh, we're already there.
It's much too quiet here.
-Too, too quiet.
-Not a good sign.
[ Bird calls ]
I sense the presence
of something evil.
-That's you.
-Zor must be at work here.
Since we left the caves,
I've had the feeling
that we're being followed.
Ah, that's me, boss.
I'm right behind you.
I don't know,
but we'll soon find out.
[ Chuckles ]
-Huh?
-Look, there they are!
-What's this?
-Come on, quick! Hide!
Oh, no, they've jumped right
into a Kurosawa film.
-So it'll start making sense?
-Mm-hm.
Yep.
-Toshiro Mifune right there.
-Goody.
I'm huge.
-Hm.
-Dig me.
Yeah?
-Oh, no, a mime.
-Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
-Did he mention he's huge?
-Yeah.
He does that.
Warriors, come out and play-ay.
[ Fighting noises ]
Now, you see,
I use two blades.
The first blade
lifts the head away
from the body before the head,
uh, can snap back
and then the, uh--
Yeah.
Yeah, below the skin level.
We get it.
Uh-huh.
Come on, come on.
Ooh, right in the breadbasket.
You know, the reason
this scene is so good
is because we care
about the characters.
-We do.
-Mm-hm.
-I mean, we do?
-Really do.
Hey, it's the life of the party.
He's got a lampshade
on his head.
Gonna be the death
of the party soon.
Oh!
Oh. Wicker armor
courtesy Pier One.
Doesn't work too well.
It's just decorative.
Hurts, don't it?
Hai. Ho.
Look out,
it's Coco the Terrible.
- [ Laughs ] Goofy old mime.
- [ Chuckles ]
Hai.
Oops.
Ouch.
Ooh.
Okay, just like we rehearsed it.
Oh.
Over, across--
[ Chuckles ]
I will kill you!
[ Laughs ]
-Aw.
-Or not.
[ Attack yells ]
Hey, is this
where the kegger is?
We saw Mark's van in front.
No, way.
Uh, we just remembered, uh,
we didn't leave enough change
in the meter.
We double-parked. Bye.
No use chasing.
Save your strength.
The castle of The Great One
is still far away.
To the end of the movie's
even further.
Well said.
-Yes.
-What I mean is...
Hey, matching vests.
--in stopping Ator--
ght, inadvertently, of course...
-Mm-hm.
-...also harm your daughter.
What do you say to that?
say you could drive a Mac truck
through your cues.
Tempo, tempo, pick it up!
I must admit, that as a murderer
you are most...
-...impressive.
-Mm-hm.
-But as an Andrew McCarthy fan--
-Whoo!
You will receive nothing
from me...
-...but pity.
-Aw.
-Careful, old man.
-Go to bed, old man.
-My patience has its limits.
-I'm aware of that.
As does your talents.
But I mustn't expect
too much from you.
[ Laughs ]
Patience, after all,
is a virtue which is found
only in the strong.
Hm.
-You're wonderful.
-Marry me.
You do amuse me.
-Hm.
-And provoke me.
-That is love, isn't it?
-Zor.
Hm.
What is it?
-Ator has escaped again.
-D'oh.
Hi, Curt Gowdy here.
Join Thong and Phil Harris
and me out on the Idaho River,
fishing for trout.
Hey, hey, now try catching
a steak, Dong.
-Thong.
-Uh, Thong. [ Chuckles ]
Uh, Ator, what's your dream?
How big is God?
For a moment back there,
I had the feeling you knew
those men that attacked us.
-Did you?
-Yes.
Well, we played
varsity together.
I do.
Who were they?
They're the survivors
of the noble tribe of Han.
They worship the God of War...
Soko.
Soko? I know that name.
-Oh, he dated my friend Sharon.
-Lord of the northern territory.
Uh, what's, uh,
Miles sitting on?
I don't wanna know.
In a great battle
against the Han,
Zor exterminated them.
But spared the lives
of three samurai
and then used them to kill
his own brother
and usurp power.
Oh, if this is
another flashback,
I gotta go get a sandwich.
-Do you think that Zor will--
-Oh, it's okay.
Do you think my father's
still alive?
Oh, sure. [ Laughs ]
Zor wants to possess
your father's knowledge, Mila.
-And your mother's wardrobe.
-Ooh.
-And the geometric nucleus.
-Hmm.
No... your father's safe
so long as he has it.
Uh, that's enough fish, Dong.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Dong.
That's enough fish.
Just a few dozen more.
Why did you go
and live so far away?
Well, it's on the bus line.
Your father taught me the path
I must follow.
It is for this
I live the way I do.
Mm-hm.
But shouldn't a man's destiny...
Oh, I thought you were gonna
say something else.
...put aside the desires
of his heart?
Man's destiny is always
predetermined...
Oh, he's a Calvinist.
...by the true desires
of his heart.
I know what mine is, and I
must follow it alone, Mila.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to pry.
That's all right.
I'm glad you asked.
What's your major?
Thong?
-Mm-hm?
-The fish is ready.
Oh, wow.
What I wouldn't give
for a Weed Eater right now.
Hm?
[ Singing ]
La la la de dah
-Hm?
-No! Don't kill us.
Uh, what will you give me?
Okay, you talked me into it.
Huh, what?
Mom and Dad, Uncle Dave?
Oh.
[ Clears throat ]
-Mila.
-What is it?
Someone's coming. Look.
-Cover your hip.
-Get dressed.
-Who are you?
-Uh, we're pirates.
-What do you want?
-Look, you captured us.
[ Clears throat ]
Line.
-Where do you come from?
-Everywhere and nowhere.
Mm-hm.
-Somebody say something.
-Well, answer.
Can't you speak?
We're from Sulijen.
[ Buzzer noise ] Wrong answer,
but thanks for playing.
Sulijen?
Yes. It's to the north,
not far from here.
-Yeah, I worked out there.
-I know.
It's where my parents
were born.
Then you're... Ator.
You're called The Great Master.
Yep. Yeah,
that's me pretty much.
Speak not in fear with me.
Much evil has fallen
on the people of our village.
In order to survive,
we must make an offering
to the god of the Kung.
Human sacrifice to the serpent
god on every full moon.
Besides, our people
are not warriors.
We're only poor farmers.
If we don't get help soon,
we'll all die.
Hm, I like it.
Make it shorter, I'll buy it.
The Kungs have always
demanded the blood of Man.
-Yeah, they're funny that way.
-We must act quickly.
But not right now.
In a minute or two.
Half an hour maybe.
Wow, check out the way
that guy moves, huh?
What do you intend to do, Ator?
We'll take them back
to the village,
and I'll speak
with their people.
-The Village People?
-Mm-hm.
The Kungs will kill us!
I... think...
-We should run!
-Run!
-Ah!
-No. Let them go, Thong.
If you love something,
let it go.
Fear has blinded them.
We'll go without them.
We'll hurry down there.
Who will be the first
to volunteer?
I'll be doing the death scene
from Camille, thank you.
Hm.
And the next?
Come forward,
Cowardly Lion.
Oh, it's a woman.
Mm-hm.
Hm.
-I could use a man like you.
-And I do mean use.
-Uh, you, uh, never mind.
- [ Chuckles ]
-Nice try.
-Yeah.
-We need another.
-I'll go.
Uh, no, you went last time.
One to a customer.
Oh, no, not you, my dear.
Our family's already given
one life to the Kung.
Grandmother, else another
will have to take my place.
-Nancy Walker in a cameo role.
-Hm.
-Wait!
-Hey!
It's Speedy Delivery Guy,
and has he got a package.
-Stop!
-In the name of love.
Just wait for me.
I'll be down in a minute.
Just stand there.
I'm coming.
-[ Sighs ]
-Okay. Well, now.
Oh, I thought this was
the Anderson party.
Sorry. [ Chuckles ]
I'll just be on my way.
Who is this gentle stranger
with pecs like melons
and knees of fringe?
Ator.
Where?
You have chosen a day
of mourning
to visit the village
of your parents.
Afternoon? Really?
I've come to help you fight.
We're not fighting men.
-The Kungs are--
-You must.
If you go on like this,
none of you will be left alive.
[ Goofy chuckles ]
Dude looks like a lady.
Where's Ravani?
-Who?
-Ravani has left us.
'Cause he had nothing to do
with the film.
He was too old to guide us.
I have taken his place
as the elder.
He was a proud,
courageous man.
But dumber
than a bag of hammers.
He never would have allowed
such submissive behavior.
-What, did you call me a wussie?
-Mm-hm.
You must not lose heart.
-I see great courage here.
-Because a guy will eat it.
Most of your young people
willingly sacrifice themselves
-to be victims of the Kungs...
-Coffee?
-...and their serpent god.
-Tea?
-Nuts.
-Put that courage to better use
and fight back,
for the Kungs can be defeated,
and I will help you.
You will regain your freedom
and live in peace again.
Surprise is an excellent weapon.
-Hi, Estelle.
How you doing, Mickey?
One of intelligence
rather than brute strength.
Posture, people.
-Let's snap it up a bit.
-But they are stupid as well.
It's Gary.
They always make frontal attacks
against their enemies.
They know you have been pacified
and won't be expecting
any resistance from you.
Uh-huh.
What we must do is prepare
a trap for them
when they arrive.
Right here.
And then we'll take them
by surprise.
-Mm-hm.
-The village is well-situated.
And so am I.
Those rocks will act as a wall
to protect you.
And vice versa.
That side is impassible
to horses,
so they'll have to attack
from over there.
To fortify that exposed side,
I'll need several sharp stakes,
ropes and three men to help me.
You and you two...
come with me.
-You afraid?
-N-- No. [ Nervous laugh ]
Won't you fight
to save your people?
No. I will.
-I wanna fight.
-For my right to party.
-Who else will join him?
-All done back there?
Aren't there any more
of you here
worthy of being called men?
Come on, we can win.
I'm sure of it. Step forward.
Or are you no better
than sheep...
...who are led to the slaughter?
Baa. [ Laugh ]
-...too harshly. We are people--
-We need more Calgon.
My husband's some hot shot.
Ancient Chinese secret, huh?
Ator's prehistoric cave dwellers
of Milwaukee
are a long way apart.
But they have
one thing in common.
Caveland means
the best human hearts available,
and Milwaukee means sacred wine.
Now, Ator...
Cream or sugar?
st, let us drink to your return.
-Okay, let's do that.
-Then we will discuss your plan.
Drink it all. Sometimes
the poison's on the bottom.
--the village of your ancestors.
-May your stay--
-I've heard this part.
-For all of us.
-Hi, Walt.
I thank you
and drink to the health,
prosperity and liberty
of your people.
Hey, not bad.
Hm.
Champagne makes me giggly.
[ Giggles ]
But let us organize ourselves.
I smell a rat, a big commie rat.
I'll need your strongest men
to build defenses.
It's Timothy Leary.
I guess Liddy will have to do
the tour without him.
Let's get to work.
My name is Ravani.
Tell Ator
they're going to trap him.
Mm-hm.
Yeah, yeah.
Get some sleep, Quentin, okay?
Is your ear drained?
Good.
Hello?
Your spit bucket's full.
Okay, so, uh,
I just go now, okay?
Um, I just leave the sign on
so the maid makes the room?
Okay.
[ Hums ]
I close the door.
Are you done with your drink?
[ Evil laugh ]
We secretly switched Ator's
coffee with Folgers crystals.
Let's watch.
Huh?
-He is huge.
-Timber!
All right. Now we call this film
The Wong Dwellers. Aw, yeah.
Thong.
Thong. Yeah, Thong.
Thorry.
Satellite picture shows clouds
are coming in from the west,
but this should burn off
by about noon.
Before the dawn of time,
a race of druids.
Nobody knew who they were
or where they came from.
Cool.
Boy, that cleared up
really quick.
I told you it would.
We've been betrayed.
-Oh, darn it.
-But still alive.
-Think so?
-Thong is free.
I wonder if it wouldn't have
been easier--
if we had just kept on going
to the aid of my father.
Oh. Monday morning quarterback.
No one's life is more important
than another's.
Except mine.
Your father would have
done the same.
Wear a tiny leather bikini?
Hmm?
This is CNN, Luke.
Check it out, they worship
the Munsingwear Penguin.
Uh, pardon us, did you see
a tiny little fox
run through here?
No?
The village elder was the one
who lured you
to come to help us.
In other words, those two
were part of the plan.
Yes.
I wish they were part
of the plot.
Some of us were against it
and wanted to fight,
but the majority
were too terrified.
The elder's going
to hand you over to the Kungs.
In exchange, they promise
to stop killing our people.
-All right, who's talking?
-I can't figure it out.
-Must be the director.
-...allied with Zor.
And what happened to Ravani?
The new elder has been
slowly poisoning him,
because he knew Ravani
would warn you if he could.
Fun.
I think Ravani must be dead
by now.
Yah! Yah!
Hey, it's Teddy Roosevelt
and the Roughriders.
I think it's the Kurds.
-And whey? [ Chuckles ]
-Yes, whey.
[ Laughs ]
They are terrifying, aren't
they? With those bandanas...
And they all look
very Machiavellian
with their shirts off.
-Yeah.
-Machiavellian?
-Hiya, Phil.
-Morning, Tom.
A month has now passed,
old one.
-Have you done what you said?
-We have kept our promise.
Now you must keep yours.
I give you Ator, and in return,
our village will no longer
have to sacrifice
to your serpent god.
-Ah!
-Uh, that must mean "no".
-I think so.
-Oh!
Grr!
Yeehoo!
[ Screaming ]
These are the pillage people.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Screaming ]
-No!
It's not fair. I'm the star
of the show. [ Sobs ]
Oh, duh, I'm sure.
My hair is getting singed.
Last time I go club-hopping
with this guy.
Honey,
start lighting those huts.
The other two...
We'll get them later.
A job well done.
No!
Please.
Oh.
Looks like the back lot
at Universal.
No, no, ah!
Feel the burn.
Come on, go for the burn.
Hey, here's just a wild idea:
why don't you rotate
to the other side of the pole,
where the fire isn't?
This scene brought to you
by Kingsford Charcoal.
Edges light quickly.
You know, they shouldn't have
filmed this at Yellowstone.
-Yay!
-All right.
All right. Finally.
-Oh.
-Aw.
-It's them again.
-Yeah.
I'll probably rip this out.
It was there when we moved in.
Good foundation, though.
Had a little trouble
with silverfish,
but that's just for a few weeks
in the spring.
Aw, hiya, Phil.
How's the snake hangin'?
-I love that joke.
- [ Chuckles ]
That's a cute story.
Hey, who's the new guy?
They're so sad.
Somebody say something.
Geez.
And that guy with the beard
really looks bitter.
Yeah.
I'm the best-looking man
in the middle ages. My, my, my!
Hi, Fred.
Hi, everyone.
Looking good, Simone.
Sorry I'm late.
Hi.
-Hello.
-Hey. What are you lookin' at?
Here is the treasure I owe you.
You can count it.
I don't mind.
And I trust you will also accept
a little personal offering.
-Thanks.
-From me to your god.
It's a new car! [ Cheering ]
Oh. Sorry.
The Bangles?
I want to thank you
for your offering,
though it weren't
in our agreement.
Oh, close your robe.
But do not think you'll be able
to exchange Ator...
-...or the girl for them.
-Darn.
It will be my honor--
to perform the rites
of sacrifice personally.
I used the word "offering"
precisely because
I didn't expect
anything in exchange from you.
I'm trying to say I'm sorry.
I consider
our mutual agreement...
to be entirely fulfilled.
Hi-- I don't-
-Your father is safe and well.
-In Hell.
Unfortunately, I won't be able
to say the same to him of you.
Or of you to him or, uh,
well, never mind.
All my efforts
to have you freed...
Don't touch the hair.
I work on the hair
and you touch it.
...don't mean a thing.
It's obvious you're not cut out
for good deeds.
Anyway, it will be
less repugnant
to be strangled
by a thousand serpents
than to have to endure
your smile.
I see. What does, uh,
"repugnant" mean again?
Oh, no matter.
Uh-huh.
Hm, yes, well.
You don't find me repugnant,
do you?
-Hm.
-You have defeated my magician.
You have defeated my warriors.
But all your science
has proved helpless
against the powers
of imagination and cunning.
May I just, uh,
cup one of your pecs?
I was sure
that your weak point...
-Ding, dong.
-...was your goodness.
Your eagerness for good deeds
has betrayed you, Ator.
The master won't be very pleased
with his prize pupil.
Tits all over-- I mean,
it's all over for you, Ator.
I know we've been breast--
Best friends.
-Damn.
-Has the mighty Ator...
-Nipple.
-...nothing to say?
Shh.
-Must be cold in there.
-Mm-hm.
-I have only one thing to say.
-Plastics.
We will meet again.
Don't know where,
don't know when.
Your master
has taught me one thing:
the dividing line
between goodness...
-...and stupidity...
-Mm-hm?
...is very, very fine.
Come on, girls.
Let's go.
-Begin the sacrifice.
-Oh, wait a minute.
The tape's not cued up. Oh.
-I got it.
-Come on, move!
[ Drightened cries ]
[ Hums ]
[ Sobs ]
[ Rattle ]
Please! Oh!
-There's a maraca down there.
-Mm-hm.
Get over there!
I can't go in there.
Susan Hayward's down there.
-Whoa.
-Uh, all right.
Uh, am I late? Uh--
Hi, Travis. Uh-
Do I look good or what?
Yes, yes.
I shall now sacrifice
for all your help and
for the powerful protection--
Yeah, yeah, powerful protection.
Yeah. Uh-huh, uh-huh.
--as well as Mila,
daughter of Akronas
and Ator,
ruler of the eastern lands.
I pray that these human
sacrifices will please you.
So that you will favor us
and we can conquer
our enemies--
Think of something, Thong.
--in Your name,
mightiest of gods.
-All right, down you go.
-Oh, no!
[ Screams ]
Huh?
Hey, this isn't so bad in here.
I could really get used to this.
- [ Whimpers ]
-Kinda pleasant.
Snake problem, though.
No!
-[ Whimpers ]
-What?
-Oh, my God.
- [ Growl ]
Oh, wait a minute, folks.
We have snakes growling here.
Throw in the next one.
-Just like the other one.
-No. No!
Oh!
Hey, what happened
to the first girl?
[ Whimpers ]
[ Whimpers, screams ]
[ Wails ]
Look, I'm way over here.
Calm down, I just ate.
I can't eat another thing
for another six months.
-You're in great shape.
-[Growling]
Growling again.
[ Hissing, growling ]
[ Whimpers ]
You know, Streep
was up for this role.
Oh. Huh?
[ Chuckles ] Snakes that growl,
huh? That's-- [ Chuckles ]
The slower
and more painful the death,
the more pleased will be
the serpent god.
You know, he told me that
really in the strictest
confidence.
All right, throw down
another one.
Just like the other one.
Wait, I'm 4F. Oh!
Ah! Ah! No, please!
Man, Gomez is really
taking his time.
Come on.
[ Wails ]
Here comes the creepy mouse.
He's padding.
No!
-No!
-[ Wails ]
Oh, well.
And now the fourth victim
to please our omnipotent god.
Uh-huh.
No, no!
I beg you!
I'll just hide here
behind this chaise-lounge.
[ Wails ]
[ Hissing ]
Yeah.
Oh, this is a Comfort Rest
adjustable bed.
[ Wails ] No, no!
Oh, look. Anal retentive snakes.
They lined up the skulls.
No! [ Screams ]
Shut up. Come on.
I'd like to move that hair
out of his face. Geez.
-Yeah.
-[ Wails ]
Aw, he's taking her home
for later.
Bye.
That was neat.
All right, you're next.
Come on!
[ Whimpers ] No!
In you go.
Psst, hey, Ator,
I'm behind the filler
linoleum post over here.
Yeah, it's cool.
[ Wails ]
[ Growling ]
-What's he gonna do?
-Ow!
Ooh.
Accept, oh lord of serpents
and evil, this fifth maiden,
which we,
your servants offer you.
May your spirit and strength
be transmitted to us
so that we may reign--
Have to cut through your wrist.
Now the man.
Always knew
I would be an apostle.
Ouch, I landed
on my eight-sided dice.
[ Groans ]
Now her.
Uh-oh.
Come on, in you go.
Get in the bidet, sister.
-[ Struggles ]
-Insy-winsy, come on.
-Aha!
-Ator, look out!
-Here we go.
-[ Groans ]
Now we finally have some action.
-Oop.
-All right.
-Ator, be careful!
-Let's get busy.
Oh, no, we gotta go now.
-Oh, no.
-Just when it's getting good.
-Yeah.
-Dag gone it.
-That's just the way it is.
-Carry me.
-No.
-Forget it.
I'll kill you myself, Ator!
[ Hums ]
-Oh, say, Joel?
-Mm-hm?
Why is it when they punch
each other in this movie
it doesn't sound anything
like a punch?
Yeah, it sounds more
like a bag full of sardines
thrown against a pole barn.
Well, you're not too far off,
you skipsters.
You see, sound effects artists
use a technique
called foley to create
those sounds.
It's interesting, isn't it?
-Mm, no.
-Not really.
I don't think so. No.
I think maybe
you should humor me.
-Oh, okay.
-Sure.
-Oh, foley, what do you know?
-Very interesting.
-Sounds cool.
-Yeah, tell us.
Well, I'm glad you asked, boys.
Foley artists
use a lot of ordinary items
found around the home
or office
to create convincing
sound effects.
Oh, like the sound of, uh,
fists slamming into jaws?
Right. But let's get started
with something simple.
An easy way to make
a horse trotting
is to use a pair of coconuts.
-Oh.
-Cocy-nuts?
Right.
Now listen.
- [ Clops ]
-Ah.
It's the sound
of a quarter horse
gelding on
a cobblestone courtyard.
It's pretty convincing,
isn't it?
Yeah, but what if the horse
is on grass, hm?
Oh, you add these handy
sod muffs, okay?
Oh.
Whoa, all of a sudden
we're at Aqueduct.
Yeah, you can do
all kinds of stuff.
Like, uh, take punches.
-Oh, I'd rather not.
-Not in the mouth.
I mean-- I mean,
the sound of punches, okay?
Traditionally, a leather glove
against a heavy metal
or a heavy punching bag
was used, okay?
Heavy metal punching bag.
-Ooh.
-Oh.
But the sound
in this Ator movie
is much, much cheesier.
Right, I'm way
ahead of you, buddy.
You just use these,
uh, goggles here.
-Yeah?
-Okay?
And you use a pair of Hollywood
meat slammers, okay?
-Add your own grunts.
-Real meat.
-[ Grunts ]
-Oh.
-Ew.
-Haikiba!
-[ Grunts ]
-Like that.
-That is absolutely perfect,
-But-- But why the goggles?
-Eye protection.
Now, I want you to name me
a sound,
and I bet I can foley it.
I got it, I got it.
Uh, do-- Do the ocean.
Okay, that's easy. Just add
birdshot to a drum head.
Wow.
-Ooh.
-Say, that's cool.
-Yeah, it's neat, huh?
-Okay, I got another one.
Let's see, um,
how about the sound
of somebody's spine cracking?
Oh, that's easy. Use celery.
Make sure it's fresh.
Okay.
-Oh!
-Ah!
-Ooh.
-Whoo.
That's too easy, guys.
Gimme a hard one.
Oh, okay, I got it.
A herd of buffalo.
Oh, no problem.
Box full of hamsters.
Huh?
-Poor guys.
-Uh, did I say "buffalo"?
I meant water buffalo.
-[ Giggles ]
-Oh, well, that's simple.
You just add some milk.
-Ew.
-Uh-huh.
-Poor little guys.
-Check it out.
Well, okay now.
I got a tough one.
-Yeah?
-A rubber Wellington boot...
-...stuck in the mud.
-Oh, that's easy.
You just fill a pair of
pantyhose with some Jell-O.
-Ugh.
-Like that.
Wow.
-Oh, yeah.
-See? Easy.
Cool.
-All right, uh, do a scream.
-Yeah, that's a good one.
Do a scream.
Oh, there's a lot of ways
to do that.
But I'll show you this way.
Just take an--
For a man's voice, you just take
an Ohio Bluetip match...
-Uh-huh.
-...strike it against somebody.
-Ow!
-[ Laughs ] See?
-Ah!
-Yeah, it's simple.
Okay, now, how about
a woman's scream, Joel?
Oh, well, then, for a woman
you set fire to TV's Madam.
-Oh, that's easy enough.
-Oh, don't mind my hat!
-Oh, no! Oh!
-See, it's simple.
There she goes.
Help me, buddy.
I'm flaming!
Oh, get me some alcohol.
That's a great scream, huh?
Cool.
-Oh, help me! Help me!
-We'll be right back.
-Whoa!
-Aha!
-Oh, that was action.
-Oh, yipes.
-Yee!
-Whew.
Would be the mother lovin'...
-...pitchin of all sock puppets?
-Yes, that's what it is.
You might say
he's coilin' a cobra.
[ Laughs ]
Big time.
And you know what?
He's not slimy at all.
That's 'cause he's made
out of velour.
Yeah, that's probably it.
A planet where snakes
evolved from men.
Uh, you know, um--
you can jump in here any time.
Uh, no problem. No, I got it.
That's okay, you just stay doin'
what you're doin' over there.
That's okay.
-Quick, hand me a hanger.
-[ Chuckles ]
Just cut the wires, Ator.
Oh, oh.
This is for Kukla.
Yeah, and--
and this one's for Fran Allison.
Yeah.
I'm comin', baby boy.
Huh.
-Well.
-That was neat.
-Are you all right?
[ Sighs ]
-You got a cigarette?
-Thanks.
-Let's stay up and talk a while.
-I'm spent.
K2, rising majestically
above the Nepalese highlands.
Or not.
It's too quiet.
Too, too quiet.
Tunk, tunk.
Is there another way up
to the castle?
Behind the wall
there's a secret passage.
Maybe we could slip in
unnoticed.
We'll never free your father
without them knowing it.
How secret could it be if, uh,
he knows about it?
We'll have to fight them.
The three of us?
No, just me.
You were a big help
with the snake.
We haven't anyone else.
Gomez, you wanna take
a line, buddy?
Tunk.
If I remember correctly,
there's another way in.
Yes, it's still there.
It opens into
the underground passage.
It's a super-secret
double dog entry.
Hm.
You and Thong go in that way.
Uh, it's Dong, sir.
-No, it is Thong, is Thong.
-Thong. Thong, ah.
Do you hear something?
I could swear I heard something.
I'll keep them busy outside.
[ Crazed laughter ]
Everything's gonna be all right.
He must have something in mind.
So you live around here much?
Do you?
Oh.
-Oh, come on!
-What the--?
-[ Laughs ]
-Terrific.
Oh.
I am the luckiest boy
in the world.
I have slipped the surly
bounds of Earth
and touched the hand of God.
This is a little ridiculous.
Okay, so he kills a deer,
he tans the hides,
he stretches the skins,
he makes some anodized
aluminum frame,
he learns how to extrude
and weld
all in about five minutes, huh?
Whew.
Learned aerodynamics.
Boy, you get up here,
everything looks small.
Only one problem,
how do I get this thing down?
Oh!
Man, it looks like he flew
into an Omnimax show,
doesn't it?
-[ Hums ]
-He flew into another country.
[ Singing ] Ator flies
and so does my heart
In his kite made of string
and sticks and bamboo
-[ Sobs ]
[ Singing ] I fly along with you
It's so pretty.
[ Singing ]
I go along for the ride
[ Sobs ]
I'm not stupid
like the rest of them
-Ator, Ator, my sweet friend
-Friend...
-Huh?
-Oh.
-Oh, sorry.
[ Clears throat ]
What? Oh, that posit-- crazy--
[ Laughs ] He's killed me.
Gomez, I've invented the wheel.
Ator Thomas Peterson,
you get down here this instant.
It's not just Ator that's
flying, it's the human spirit.
Let's get outta here.
Help me, I don't know
how to get this thing to work.
-Good-bye.
-Good-bye, folks.
Good-bye.
[ Singing ] And he flies
with his stupid contraption
I think I just invented
air-sickness.
[ Laughs ]
Meanwhile, at the wineries
of Ernest and Julio Gallo--
Tommy Smothers
is raising quite a havoc.
Mm-hm.
Uh, my hub--
My hubcap's chafing.
Ooh.
Huh. This must be the secret
passageway. Let's go.
- [ Singing ] So high
-Oh.
Flying...
Great, this is the opening
of from Where Eagles Dare.
-Mm-hm.
-I've seen this.
Weyerhaeuser is committed
to preserving
our natural resources.
I can see my house from here!
[ Singing ]
We're flying so free
Hey, it's anamorphic.
Huh?
-Squished out.
-We're in Vienna?
Hey.
Hey, look up there.
-What is it? A bird?
-It's a bird!
-It's a plane! It's Superman!
-Oh, I've seen that comic.
-It's a graphic novel, Joel.
-Oh, right. I'm sorry.
Hey, Carl, this is
George Kennedy.
Uh, we're gonna
talk you down now.
You're crazy. It can't be.
Hold on.
There's a man in the sky.
Huh?
A man in the sky?
Get out of here.
Enough of your lies.
I think I blew my cover.
[ Chuckles ]
Is that Ator up there?
-Yes.
-Or are you just glad to see me?
Because I taught him
the theory of flight.
And if you had been
a better student, Zor,
you could be flying, too.
Ooh.
-Theory.
-There's those meat slammers.
Theory of flight? I'll
teach you the theory of fist!
You can go on beating me--
But knee me in the groin first.
Because Ator is better than you,
he'll vanquish you.
We'll see about that.
Oh! That one stung.
He hit on that one.
-Connected.
-Made contact.
[ Singing ]
Landing music
He's in trouble
Pretty.
I gotta land.
I'm almost outta fuel.
Huh?
Oh, it's an Alpine White
commercial.
Well, looks like he flew
into 17th century Bulgaria,
and that's Mad Ludwig's castle
right there.
[ Spitting noises ]
Ooh, right in the turret. Ooh.
[ Singing ]
Doo doo doo
Message for you, sir.
Run for your lives!
Help!
Whoo.
Oh, he also made bombs
while he was makin'
that kite there.
Oh, it looks like he's gonna
carpet bomb.
-Mm-hm.
-Yep.
Yeah.
All right, you crummy rats,
Henry Kissinger says
Merry Christmas.
[ Whistling bomb noises ]
Whoa. That's for calling me
a femme. Oh.
Oh, he didn't even throw
that one.
Damn, no handrail.
Oh, that's a nice, uh,
well-lit secret passageway.
Well, it's secret, but they
didn't wanna get carried away.
Okay, uh, thrust,
parry, advance,
cross, thrust, back, thrust...
Here's one
from my old pal Melvin Ladd!
[ Whistling bomb noises ]
-[ Screams ]
-God, they hit Charlie McCarthy.
Oh, yeah.
[ Spitting noise ]
Whoo.
Oh, I love this.
This is gonna be my regular
Saturday night thing.
Who's your old regular
Saturday night thing?
[ Singing ]
Doo doo doo, doo doo doo
-I thought the movie was done.
-Hey, what?
Oh, he's landing
in the outback now.
Oh, ah?
-How'd he do that?
-How'd I do that?
I suppose he's got a tank
in the courtyard now.
Yeah, and it's made
outta coconuts.
Right.
I think I can, I think I can,
ink I can, I think I can. Uh-oh.
This is for you. Ha!
And there's one for you. Ha!
There's a little bit more
for you.
That stung.
Thank you.
Pardon me. Thank you.
Coming through.
I know the nucleus
is in here somewhere.
And you had better tell me
where it is.
He'd probably tell you if
you'd stop pushin' him around.
Or I'll kill you
with my own bare hands.
I'm warning you.
Now, tell me,
where have you hidden it?
It's over by the protons,
you can't miss it.
[ Groaning ]
If I can't have it, nobody will.
Hey, he's gonna cut the heck
out of his thighs
with those swords.
No!
-You will die!
-No.
Ator!
-Tadaa!
Come on.
They call me Atra,
and I don't come
with a comfort strip.
I'm not afraid of you.
-Okay, well, maybe a little.
-Hm.
So the mighty Ator
needs two swords
to fight with, does he?
ry is the ignorant man's weapon.
[ Grunts ]
Aha.
So the mighty longhaired
John Saxon
needs two swords to fight.
Fight!
-Fight.
-Is this the mighty Ator...
-Uh, no, that's a pole.
-...the living legend?
Wait, who said "living legend"?
Have you lost your nerve?
Oh, come on.
Yeah, he ran to the ends
of the earth,
he invented the wheel,
he's had a long day.
Long day.
Look, the Desiderata's
on the wall over there.
It's the original.
-Fight!
-Not gonna help him now.
Uh-uh.
He's not much
without his hang glider, is he?
[ Chuckles ]
No!
No.
Oh, no.
-[ Grunts ]
-You have wonderful pecs.
Made you blink.
No.
Is that a comic book
over there--?
It's not a comic book,
it's a graphic novel.
It's a graphic novel.
-For crying out loud.
-It's not good enough.
Okay, now that-- that's good.
-Can he do that?
-Now I'll cut you in two.
-Into what?
-[ Laughs ]
[ Attack grunts ]
Oh, bad place.
Oh, oh, ouch.
Owie, ow, ow, owie.
No, Ator, you can't.
Zor is disarmed.
If you kill him now,
you'll be guilty of murder.
Wait until he is tried
by the high court
of the league of peaceful lands.
Oh, he's making that up.
-What is this, BC Law?
-They will see justice is done.
They will make him pay
for his crimes,
but for us to take the law
into our hands
puts on the level
of the barbarian.
We are barbarians.
To destroy life isn't something
Man should take upon himself.
What are you,
Lucas Tanner all of a sudden?
So what the heck did I
hang glide in here for anyway?
Could've wrapped that up sooner.
Now, beat it.
[ Chuckles ]
Ator, be careful!
-[ Grunts ]
-Huh?
-Hurts, don't it?
-Give my mustache to... Trevor.
[ Gasps ]
Trevor.
Hey, thanks a lot, Dong.
I'll visit you in prison,
bake you a rice cake
with a saw in it, buddy.
-I mean, thanks.
-Father! Ator!
-Are you all right?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
Is Charles in Charge over?
Thanks for showing up.
Thank goodness you're safe.
[ Gasps ]
[ Sobs ]
-Hey, come on.
-Thanks to Ator...
How about a little sugar
for Ator over here? Huh? Hm?
Thong?
No, it's a dance belt.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Your father gave me the nucleus.
I'm taking it back with me.
Oh, and, uh, there was some
turkey and stuff in the fridge.
I made myself a sandwich.
Hope you don't mind.
Mila, I wanted to say that...
You don't have to say anything.
I know you must fight evil
wherever it occurs.
My life is too dangerous
to share with you.
Mm-hm.
You must follow your destiny.
Alone.
With Chad.
Good-bye, Mila.
After I've finished,
I'll be back.
And I'll look
like a leather pancake.
Yes.
Take care of yourself and
your father. He needs you.
[ Laughs ]
Uh, I gotta go model for a line
of action figures. I'll see you.
-Watch over them, Thong.
-I think I can do that.
He is, like, so cool!
Oh.
Miles O'Keefe will be back
in Where Angels Go,
Trouble Follows.
Hey, feedback. Neat.
Lest the nucleus fall
into unscrupulous hands,
and the Earth
and all living creatures
be consumed in a seething
cauldron of annihilation...
-Anybody got a clue?
-...Ator destroyed it.
-Hm.
-Perhaps in the future...
...Man would be wise enough
to use this Promethean...
Actually, Mrs. O'Leary's cow
kicked it over.
-Ah.
-Oh, yeah.
Mankind, you make me
want to vomit.
Go away, just go away.
I'm so sick of you.
Get outta here.
Come on.
Well, this is neat,
but what the heck does it
have to do with the movie?
Uh... uh.
your guess is as good as mine.
Think they ran out
of things to do.
Yeah.
Throw a little Oppenheimer
in here right now.
Hey, I see a president's face
up there.
I see a bunny.
Huh.
-Ah, but enough of this.
-[ Laughs ]
-Let's escape to Wisconsin.
-Yeah.
Looks like he traded in
his hang glider for a horse.
He probably built
that horse, too.
Yeah, I bet he did.
-Out of mud and sticks.
-Raised it from a pup.
-Beautiful animal, isn't he?
-Yeah.
-Hey, look, tire tracks.
-[ Laughs ]
-God!
-The inherent goodness of Man...
The inherent dullness of riding.
...to do battle,
wherever Man's oppressed...
Wherever there's kids laughing
'cause they're hungry
-and they know supper's ready.
-...and free from bondage...
Whenever there's a cop
beating up on a guy.
...too powerful or protected
to avoid his rightful
punishment.
He is the guardian of knowledge
and the hope of the future.
-Yeah, right.
-Ator the avenger.
Whoa! Huh?
-What?
-Who are--?
Oh, the guardians of BO,
all of a sudden.
No, that's--
Those are the screenwriters.
Take your best shot, guys.
I gotta get something heavy
to throw. [ Chuckles ]
This is really cute,
these credits here, huh?
Hey, it's the new kids
in the cave.
Oh.
You know, they couldn't even
find an exciting enough scene
from their own movie
to show with the credits.
This looks like the Jefferson
Junior High production
of Godspell.
I think so, yeah.
I missed that.
-[ Rhythmic humming ]
-Uh, um, no, those--
No, no, no, no.
The Mohawk goes the other way.
You look like a turkey.
Or kind of like
a bath brush too.
Yeah.
Walk like an Egyptian.
Kakonkajong.
Hey, chicken head.
Hey, chicken head. [ Laughs ]
-Who said that?
-[ Laughs ] [ Rhythmic humming ]
Now, where is my shirt?
Apion, I need to borrow
some money.
I think he's looking
for James Franciscus
and Charlton Heston.
-[ Rhythmic humming ]
-Oh, wow.
[ Rhythmic humming ]
Kinda groovy.
Okay, let's get outta this dog
right now.
-Huh?
-Who is it?
-We gotta go.
-Oh.
Uh, oh, hi.
Hey, it's Chad and Trevor.
They found each other.
-What?
-What do you want?
Come on, what?
It wasn't that bad, was it?
Come on.
I liked it.
[ Growls ]
Look, booby,
when we send you a film,
they're supposed to be bad.
-What do you want from us?
-I mean, we--
We have it worse than them.
We have to watch you
watching the film.
[ Sighs ]
Okay, look, it's bad enough
that this was clearly the worst
film you have ever sent us,
but it was also filled with
continuity problems to boot.
Yep.
My colleague Crow
will elucidate.
-Uh, I'll what?
-You'll show 'em.
Oh, right, right.
Okay.
Uh, anyway, uh, frame 1:22:47.
Uh, Cambot, bring that up.
A pan of a field,
yet seen clearly in the back,
somebody's been four-wheelin'.
Okay, next frame, please,
uh, 2:16:25:03.
Thank you, Cambot.
Forgiving the fact that Ator
is flying a hang glider,
he's doing it.
over a modern city!
[ Sighs ]
Okay, now,
the piece of resistance.
Cambot, 2:02:0, 4, 3.
Okay, during the raping
and pillaging,
a prehistoric caveman
is clearly seen wearing
a pair of Ray-bans.
Who's that behind
the Foster Grants? It's Ogg!
Yeah, and what about
Scarecrow's brain?
Huh?
What do you want from us?
We're evil!
Evil!
Yep, I guess you could say
we're cut
from a different cloth.
-Exactly, Frank. Push the butt-
-Guess you could say
we're more evil
than a three-dollar bill.
Push the button, Frank.
Guess you could say
the factory's still open,
but we're makin'
different stuff now.
Would you just push the button?
Ah, the button.
Guess you could say
we're buying it wholesale
and passin' the savings
on to you.
Thong, the fish is ready.